<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 - NubeStack. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NubeStack delivers enterprise-grade cloud solutions, consulting, and managed services designed to simplify cloud adoption and accelerate digital transformation. We empower businesses with secure, scalable, and innovative technology, leveraging the power of open-source and cloud-native solutions to drive efficiency and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-vision&#34;&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To be the trusted partner for organizations looking to modernize IT infrastructure, harness innovation, and unlock the full potential of the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-values&#34;&gt;Our Values&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Innovation&lt;/strong&gt; – Driving continuous improvement and embracing forward-thinking technology.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrity&lt;/strong&gt; – Building trust through transparency, accountability, and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Technology&lt;/strong&gt; – Delivering opensource, future-ready solutions and avoiding vendor lock-in.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customer Success&lt;/strong&gt; – Partnering with clients to achieve measurable business outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Container Orchestration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/container-orchestration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/container-orchestration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;container-orchestration&#34;&gt;Container Orchestration&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scalable and secure Kubernetes solutions for managing containerized applications across cloud environments with enterprise-grade security and 99.9% uptime guarantee.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Sovereignty Solved: On-Prem Compliance with Ceph Storage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/success-stories/data-sovereignty-ceph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/success-stories/data-sovereignty-ceph/</guid>
      <description>How a financial services company achieved strict data residency compliance by provisioning on-prem Ceph storage clusters with NubeStack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industry Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/industry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NubeStack empowers organizations across diverse sectors to innovate, scale, and operate efficiently with tailored cloud and technology solutions. Our expertise spans telecommunications, bioinformatics, and education—delivering secure, automated, and future-ready platforms for every need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Explore how we help industries transform with advanced cloud infrastructure and automation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;telecommunication&#34;&gt;Telecommunications&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We modernize telecom networks with cloud-native NFV and automation, enabling rapid 5G deployment and seamless operations from core to edge. Our platforms leverage OpenStack, Kubernetes, and best-in-class automation to reduce OpEx and accelerate service delivery.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Cloud Agility: Kubernetes Migration and Vendor Lock-in Reduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/success-stories/multicloud-k8s-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/success-stories/multicloud-k8s-optimization/</guid>
      <description>How a technology provider achieved true multi-cloud portability and massive cost savings by standardizing on OpenStack and Kubernetes with NubeStack&amp;rsquo;s guidance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFV Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/nfv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/nfv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;nfv-solutions&#34;&gt;NFV Solutions&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Incorporate Telco and HPC grade low-latency NFV technologies like SRIOV, DPDK, and OVN to accelerate cloud network performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private/Public Cloud Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/cloud-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/cloud-solutions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;privatepublic-cloud-solutions&#34;&gt;Private/Public Cloud Solutions&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenStack, OpenShift, AWS, Azure, and GCP based cloud solutions for building, managing, and scaling private and public clouds with flexibility, security, and cost-effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-cloud-services&#34;&gt;Our Cloud Services&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Private cloud design and deployment (OpenStack, OpenShift)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Public cloud migration and management (AWS, Azure, GCP)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hybrid and multi-cloud strategies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enterprise-grade security and compliance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;99.9% uptime guarantee&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;24/7 support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ready to transform your business with the right cloud solution? &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/contact&#34;&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust in Google Cloud: Mitigating Data Exfiltration Risk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/success-stories/zero-trust-google-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/success-stories/zero-trust-google-cloud/</guid>
      <description>A global e-commerce platform successfully implemented a Zero Trust architecture and VPC Service Controls on Google Cloud with NubeStack to protect sensitive assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening Cloud Security with Zero Trust and VPC Service Controls</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As organizations continue their digital transformation journeys, securing cloud environments has become more critical than ever. Traditional perimeter-based security is no longer sufficient in a world where workloads are distributed across hybrid and multi-cloud environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enter the &lt;strong&gt;Zero Trust model&lt;/strong&gt; — a modern approach to cloud security that assumes no user, device, or service is inherently trusted. Combined with &lt;strong&gt;Google Cloud’s VPC Service Controls&lt;/strong&gt;, enterprises can significantly reduce data exfiltration risks, strengthen compliance, and maintain strict control over sensitive assets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Data Sovereignty Challenges and On-Prem Storage Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/02/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As enterprises increasingly adopt cloud technologies, &lt;strong&gt;data sovereignty and compliance&lt;/strong&gt; have become critical concerns. Organizations must ensure that &lt;strong&gt;sensitive data remains within specific geographic or regulatory boundaries&lt;/strong&gt; while still enabling modern cloud workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NubeStack helps enterprises address these challenges by provisioning &lt;strong&gt;on-prem Ceph storage clusters&lt;/strong&gt;, allowing &lt;strong&gt;public and private workloads to access data securely&lt;/strong&gt; without ever leaving the organization’s premises.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware State and OpenStack Migrations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Virtualization has been the backbone of modern IT infrastructure for over a decade. VMware continues to be a dominant player, powering enterprise data centers with robust virtualization, management tools, and integrated solutions. However, many organizations are now exploring &lt;strong&gt;OpenStack&lt;/strong&gt; as a &lt;strong&gt;flexible, open-source alternative&lt;/strong&gt; to reduce vendor lock-in, enable cloud-native workloads, and achieve cost optimization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we explore the current state of VMware environments, the challenges organizations face during migration, and how &lt;strong&gt;NubeStack&lt;/strong&gt; can help enterprises &lt;strong&gt;successfully transition to OpenStack-based cloud solutions&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/devops/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital landscape, organizations must deliver software faster, more securely, and more reliably than ever before. &lt;strong&gt;DevOps Services&lt;/strong&gt; bridge the gap between development and operations teams — enabling seamless collaboration, continuous integration, and automated delivery pipelines that accelerate innovation and reduce time to market.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Nubestack&lt;/strong&gt;, we bring together the best of development, automation, and operations to build high-performing, resilient, and scalable delivery systems tailored to your business needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Automation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/automation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Building and managing modern cloud infrastructure involves a multitude of repetitive and error-prone tasks — from provisioning servers and configuring networks to deploying complex workloads across multiple environments. &lt;strong&gt;Infrastructure Automation&lt;/strong&gt; transforms this process by replacing manual operations with code-driven, consistent, and scalable workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Nubestack&lt;/strong&gt;, we help organizations automate every layer of their infrastructure — ensuring faster deployments, reduced human error, improved reliability, and greater agility across the entire lifecycle of your cloud environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managed Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/managed-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/managed-services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast-paced digital world, managing complex cloud environments can be challenging and time-consuming. &lt;strong&gt;Managed Services&lt;/strong&gt; are designed to take that burden off your shoulders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In simple terms, &lt;em&gt;Managed Services&lt;/em&gt; mean that a specialized provider like &lt;strong&gt;Nubestack&lt;/strong&gt; takes full responsibility for the day-to-day management, monitoring, and maintenance of your cloud infrastructure — ensuring it runs smoothly, securely, and efficiently, around the clock.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of worrying about software upgrades, downtime, or infrastructure health, you get a dedicated team of experts who handle it all for you — so your internal teams can focus on building applications and delivering business value.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Message Sent Successfully</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact-success/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you for contacting us! We&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;our-services&#34;&gt;Our Services&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;cloud-solutions&#34;&gt;Cloud Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We provide comprehensive cloud infrastructure and deployment solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;web-development&#34;&gt;Web Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Custom web applications and responsive websites built with modern technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mobile-app-development&#34;&gt;Mobile App Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Native and cross-platform mobile applications for iOS and Android.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;devops--infrastructure&#34;&gt;DevOps &amp;amp; Infrastructure&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Continuous integration, deployment pipelines, and infrastructure automation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;consulting-services&#34;&gt;Consulting Services&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Technical consulting and architecture design for your projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
